

Profile

Passionate problem solver with more than 15 years of customer service experience. Always, willing to go that extra mile to help people feel 100% satisfied with the service they receive. Fluent in Spanish but also in interpersonal skills. I love to help and always do so with a smile. "Because life is always changing, so should you!" is my motto.

Employment History

Property Manager, Barrett Property Management Inc, Nevada City May 2018 - Present

- Main responsibilities include managing vacation rentals which includes handling inquiries, maintaining accurate calendars and scheduling cleaners.
- Secondary responsibilities include conducting move in and move out inspections, showing of homes to potential new tenants.

Self Employed

May 2012 - May 2018

- Some of the work includes indoor and outdoor painting of homes.
- Small home repairs such as wall patch, deck repair, outdoor residing, etc.
- Purchasing and completely remodeling two neighboring duplex properties.
- Converting the two smaller units of the said properties into fully furnished vacation rentals.
- · Managing all aspects of the vacation rentals.

Education

UC Davis Continuing and Professional Education, Sacramento Certificate Of Completion Full Stack Web Development

Dec 2019 - Jun 2019

Completed all necessary courses, homework and projects to receive a certificate of completion for UC Davis boot camp for full stack web development.

Details

535 Butler ST Grass Valley, CA 95945 (530) 210-7717 aldovibanco85@gmail.com

Skills

Coding

Customer Service

Communication

Typing Skills

Bilingual

Problem Solving

Hobbies

Running, cooking, interior designing, photography, photo editing, gardening, gaming, traveling.

Languages

Spanish

Education continued...

Allied Real Estate Schools (Online Program), Grass Valley CA

Nov 2017 - Jan 2018

Completed all necessary courses and hours to take the State exam to obtain Salesperson license. State Exam passed and received Real Estate Salesperson License.

Glendale Community College, Glendale CA

Aug 2011 - May 2012

Completed several general ed classes and several art and design classes to work towards obtaining an Associates of Arts and Science Degree.

Lone Star College System, Kingwood TX

Jan 2010 - May 2011

Completed several general ed classes and several art and design classes to work towards obtaining an Associates of Arts and Science Degree.

Extra-Curricular Activities

Avid Member at Gold Country Kiwanis, Grass Valley, CA

Jan 2017 - Present

Gold Country Kiwanis is an organization of members that help the local community and children. Our organization completes service projects around the community, raises money and donates to other local charities and sponsors several scholarships for the local youth. Personal contributions and responsibilities include, managing the group's website and creating distributing the e-newsletter.

References

Amelia Barrett Broker (Owner) Barrett Property Management Inc. amelia@barrettpm.com (530) 470-3272

Justin Gross Voice Over Actor (Owner) Justin Gross Inc. justinmaxgross@yahoo.com (818) 692-1152

Lisa Swanson (Owner) Dharma Accupuncture lisaswanson74@gmail.com (530) 648-4192

Details

535 Butler ST Grass Valley, CA 95945 (530) 210-7717 aldovibanco85@gmail.com

Skills

Coding

Customer Service

Communication

Typing Skills

Bilingual

Problem Solving

Hobbies

Running, cooking, interior designing, photography, photo editing, gardening, gaming, traveling.

Languages

Spanish